[Heo Seong-jin’s ‘Finish Line’]
[noisy]
[Player] Left foot, left foot
[Soft music]
[Dongju/Narration]
Time seemed to stop so slowly
It was clear and clear
[Player] Left foot
[Dongju/Narration] The sound of breathing and
I could even see beads of sweat on the gloves.
But
That punch was unavoidable.
An unexpected blow struck while defenseless.
The moment you see it with your own eyes
It's already too late
- [Eerie sound effect]
- [Hannah] Hey, Dongju Yoon, are you okay?
Dongju Yoon
[Dongju/Narration] Avoid it
It's not something you can avoid.
[Hannah] Are you okay?
[Dongju/Narration]
My whole body loses strength
I can't move a single finger.
[Soft music]
hazy and distant
as if drunk
[Hannah] Yoon Dong-ju
Dongju Yoon
Then
It's okay
[sigh]
[Dongju/Narration] Love
It's coming
[Dongju] Oh, look at that bastard
What did you see?
Look at this bastard
Do you want to keep joking? huh?
I told you to go to the hospital
I can't even listen to you.
Jjunguljjungul
[Tense music]
[sigh]
[Jonghyun] Min Joo-young
Around 02:10 on the 13th
Jinsu Lee, who was leaving work after working overtime.
Died in hit-and-run traffic accident
A week later, around 03:00 on the 20th
Lee Gyeong-il, the hit-and-run perpetrator, surrendered himself.
Suicide in prison
5 days later, around 05:30 on the 25th
Vehicle smuggler Monkey Party Kim Deok-chul is murdered.
This incident and I
What's the connection?
That bastard, Mr.
Monkey School Kim Deok-chul
Vehicles, illegal weapons, drugs, etc.
Via Russia and the Philippines
I was smuggling
For customs clearance of goods
I even forged documents.
for forging documents
It's difficult without internal stakeholders.
- You know it well, right?
- Yes
[Jonghyun] The person in charge of that task
Jinsu Lee
And the former person in charge
It's Min Joo-young himself.
Hit Jinsu Lee
Found a hit-and-run vehicle
The National Forensic Service is currently investigating
Whose DNA will be found there?
Let's wait and see
What evidence will come out?
[Jooyoung] I guess you weren’t really hurt?
I thought you were hospitalized
[Dongju] Putting you in jail
I'm going to go see it
I'm going to get a proper diagnosis, so be prepared.
you are done now
[Jooyoung] So recklessly
arrest a person
You make things so easy.
Easy?
me
I'm risking my life
[Jooyoung] No,
You have to risk your life from now on.
From now on
[tick tock]
[Jonghyun] Min Joo-young
Why do you check the time like that?
It's just a habit
When working, you can check the arrival and departure times
I need to check carefully.
today
I guess there's something coming in.
[Beep]
[Dongju] That bastard
I'm thinking of crushing it on your ass.
- Never open your mouth.
- [Mansik] Yes
If this continues, request a warrant.
I think it's going to be difficult
[Mansik] No,
There's still time to spare
Didn’t it happen when the National Forensic Service came out with the results?
Let me check again
Oh, I just have to screw it up.
- I'm not the kind of guy who can communicate with words.
- [Mansik] Yes
Why do you keep saying ‘yes’, team leader?
- [Knock knock knock]
- [Click - Moon]
[dark music]
Excuse me
[Mansik] What are they again?
[Dongju] Ah, I have to catch that bastard.
Why are you taking me away?
Why are you taking me away so suddenly?
[Investigator] Just stay still.
Really since last time
Why are you sitting still?
You look still, now?
- [Jaehong] Stop it!
- Oh, that doesn't make sense!
[Jaehong] I’ll let you go only if you stop.
Ah...
[Jaehong] Don’t do it
Tsk
sorry
[Investigator] First of all, Min Joo-young
On suspicion of smuggling
At Inseong Headquarters Customs
This case has been handed over to the prosecution.
Suspect under the Customs Act
You know you have to hand it over, right?
This is a related official document.
Hey, I can't see well because I'm presbyopic.
Hey
- [Tense music]
- [Seokhyun] What?
What do you have to say?
A busy prosecutor
Because of just one criminal
You came here directly like this?
Also from dawn?
Brother, I know you don’t like me.
- This is not it.
- Hey
Do I look that leisurely?
Do you know that some people do it because they want to?
If a government official tells you to do it, you should do it.
Is there anything special?
I've been so annoying since dawn, shit.
[Investigator] Prosecutor, police chief
I want to see you for a moment.
yes, i understand
Get out of the way
[Jonghyun sighs]
[bang]
[Hannah] Minjooyoung, wait a minute.
Let me ask you one thing.
Where did you get that watch?
I received a gift
To whom?
Why are you asking that?
[Hannah] That watch
Watches distributed domestically
I'm assuming it's not
Really?
Maybe so.
A Russian friend gave it to me as a gift.
The name is
Because it was so long ago
I can't remember.
Coincidentally
There are suspicions of collusion with that side.
Lee Sang-gon of the Golden Rabbit School
Oh Jong-gu, CEO of J9 Security
They were wearing the same watch
At the scene of Lee Gyeong-il’s death,
The watch was found
Do you have similar tastes?
Well, I guess it was a coincidence.
Really?
I don't think it's a coincidence
[nervous music]
That female police officer
You often appear on TV
famous national shooting athlete
This is where I see the shooting fairy.
But the name...
This is Inspector Ji Hanna.
Inspector Ji is on his watch.
You seem to be quite interested.
So would you like to see it for yourself?
Is it the same?
[Seokhyun] What are you doing? I won't take you quickly
Next time you see me, please give me an autograph.
Ha, what are you doing?
don't get close
Uh oh
- [Seokhyun] Hey!
- [Dongju] Let go!
- Oh, come out! really
- [Seokhyeon] Mr...
[Mansik] Hey, man!
[Small] Do you want to beat up the prosecutor?
Ah, then just like this
Just stay still?
Prosecutor or whatever, what do I know!
- [Seokhyun] This bastard has really started since last time.
- [Dongju] Hey!
Hey, you, I must
I'll throw you in jail
If you can run away, go!
- I will chase you until the end...
- [Tinnitus beeping]
[Mansik] Hey, hey, hey
- [Heavy music]
- Hey, Mr. Why are you like this?
[Cluck cluck]
[groan]
Why is this happening?
I think I said the same thing before.
I couldn't answer you.
- [Eerie sound effect]
- If you can try anything, try it.
Because I'll look forward to it
This guy is real
Are you okay?
From my own health
I think you should take care of it.
Go to the hospital quickly
Don't get too upset
[Dongju] Lee, sir, sir...
[Mansik] Stop it, hey, move it
[Jonghyun and Jaehong’s encouraging sounds]
[click - car door]
- Let's go.
- [Investigator] Yes
[Roaring]
- [click - car door]
- [groan]
[Seokhyun] Yes, manager
I brought you out now
yes, i understand
[Beep]
Ah...
lose shape
Escort this common criminal
Hey
What are you doing you bastard?
What is this?
Even the chief prosecutor himself came forward?
Are you a relative?
no
[Seokhyun] A junior at school?
[Seokhyun] No, then what are you?
[Jooyoung] I’m a civil servant.
Same as that one
[Meaningful music]
- [ticking]
- [Jooyoung’s sigh]
It's okay
So the hospital
If you leave without permission
Can you do it or not?
sorry
[Doctor] Yes
Well, don't worry too much.
These are symptoms of a mild concussion.
Detailed tests are
Maybe I should give it a try
After being hospitalized for a few days,
It'll be okay
Where's the next patient?
[Nurse] I’m going to the examination room.
[Mansik] Ugh
Anyway, I'm not listening
Installed it and it works well, huh?
Until you get better
Just lie here quietly, okay?
What about that kid?
No, how are you going to catch it without me?
well
Oh, don't nag me
Take the test well, tsk
[Nurse] I’m going to the examination room.
I'm going
To my family
Shouldn't we contact you?
[Wing - Cell Phone]
He has no one, he's alone
Baby, what are you trying to scratch?
Another call, huh?
Why, what is it?
Yeah, okay
- [Beep]
- Hey, I have to go into the office.
I guess something happened again
Oh, and
Dong-ju asks Inspector Ji to take a look.
Me?
yes
Even if no one else knows that guy
You listen carefully to Inspector Ji. I have a favor to ask.
- [Jaehong] Please
- [Hannah] Yes
[Roaring - door]
[Tense music]
What is it, huh? What is it?
why?
[Jaehong] I understand
Team leader
I received a call from the National Forensic Service.
All related materials
The prosecution took it.
Even the confiscated vehicles.
[Daeyong] I understand that this is how I ended up.
Our senior’s heart
- [Mansik] Why are you like this, so disgusting?
- Ah, ah...
Ha...
The prosecution swept it all away.
Even a little bit with that civil servant.
All related incidents
Lee Jin-soo hit and run, Golden Rabbit
Everything, even Monkey
Ah, Minjooyoung, that bastard.
What on earth are you doing?
I want to know too, what are you doing?
[Jooyoung] But the name is...
[Hanna] This is Inspector Ji Hanna.
[clatter]
[Calm music]
[Staff 1] To ensure that there are no shortage of players
Check the quantity carefully
- [Staff 2] Okay.
- [Staff 3] Yes
[Staff 1] If the quantity is correct,
Leave me a box
[Staff 3] Yes, I understand.
[click click]
- [Reporter 1] I'm going, I'm going
- [Reporter 2] Let’s go, let’s go
[Reporter 3] Ji Hanna fighting
[Reporter 4] Hanna
Please just look over here
[Reporter 5] Please take a look here too.
What are you doing, really, Mr.
[Reporters’ cheering]
Oh, I'm really going crazy.
[Reporter 1] Please take a look here.
- [Reporter 2] Please take a look here.
- [Bang! Bang!]
[Hannah] Eat well as usual
Taking good care of my condition
We are preparing
[Reporter 1] Preparation for the Sao Paulo game
How are you doing?
[Reporter 2] Then again this time
Are you confident of winning the gold medal?
[Hanna/Video] Ah, oh, it’s cold
Ha...
Is anyone there?
uh?
Bbangyahoppang in the cold winter
Eat some hoppang and go.
[Shooting player 1]
Hey, you've become a big star, really.
Filming an ad like that
Do all your team training at night, Mr.
[Hanna/Video] Bread, bread
[Shooting player 2]
What can I do, the national fairy?
- You said you don't have time.
- [Shooting Player 3] That's how you become Jihanna
I only know one thing
[Shooter 2] But did you hear?
Ji Hanna broke up with Kim Jong-hyun.
[Shooting player 3]
Huh! Why, why, why, why, why?
[Shooting Player 2] Why would you do it? It’s obvious.
Who can handle Ji Hanna’s personality?
[Shooting athletes laugh]
[Shooting Player 3] Bbang, Bbang, Bbang
[Shooting player 2]
Don't do it, be quiet
child, Mr.
You throw away things like this so carelessly
I get upset when I see buns
They say so much
[Shooting Player 1] Hoppang was so delicious
[Shooting Player 2] Ji Hanna
I'll enjoy the buns
Hoppang
[Dongju] That’s all
It's because I'm jealous
Hey
A gold medal that is hard to win
Because you win so easily
I'm grumpy for no reason
What can I say
There is such a thing as the fate of geniuses
That feeling of being surrounded by envy and jealousy
What
I know it well
Oh, I'm taking all of this.
Judo Mincheol
Gold medal sticker appears
I heard you won the selection contest.
I get some of that energy too
I guess I lost again?
Because I believe that
My skills aren't improving
Hey, I'm the Asian champion
I'm just unlucky these days.
[Louder] Than people who hate you
There are more people who like it!
[HYNN’s ‘Embrace me, with love’]
I like you too!
♪ Sent countless times ♪
♪ Your kind words ♪
♪ Mmm ♪
♪ Your eyes ♪
♪ Voice ♪
♪ Your heart ♪
♪ Gradually it seeps into me ♪
♪ Warmly ♪
♪ Hug me ♪
♪ With love ♪
♪ Always be by your side ♪
♪ Always ♪
♪ Now I finally realize ♪
♪ Just always ♪
♪ To you who waited ♪
♪ Approach with a small breath ♪
♪ I'll hug you ♪
[Roaring - door]
Huh, ah, why is this happening?
Stick it somewhere like this
Oh! Give it to me
I don't like it, it's mine, but you gave it to me
Hey, give it to me
- I don't like it, I gave it to you, but where can I take it?
- [Hannah] Baby, give it to me.
- It's hard to find.
- [Hannah] Baby, give it to me!
- Oh, I hate it, I hate it!
- [Hannah] Hey
Ah...
♪ Always be by your side ♪
♪ Always ♪
♪ Now I finally realize ♪
- [Nurse] I’ll wake up.
- [Stopping music]
I'll go to my seat.
- Wow
- [Tap-tap-tap]
Hey, it's torn into pieces.
I'll lie down
[Hannah] Oh, are you here?
[Jonghyun] Oh
- [Nurse] It will sting.
- [Dongju] Oh, wait, wait a minute.
- Wait, oh, wait.
- [Nurse] Tingling
- [Dongju] Wait, wait, wait a minute
- Yoon Dong-ju seems to be okay now.
- [Dongju] Argh!
Oh, wait a minute for you.
I'm here to tell you something, Hannah.
[Atmospheric music plays]
[Hannah] Thank you
[Jonghyun] Oh, that
Earlier during the day...
It's okay
fact
From Minjooyoung’s side
I feel like I'm watching you
I think the government stole your information.
Inside the office?
[Jonghyun] Oh
Probably Jinsu Lee's documents
Maybe you think you saw it?
Do you remember what it was?
[sigh]
How much do you know now
I don't know so I'm just watching
As the investigation progresses and the closer we get,
I don't know how they'll come out
Because it could be dangerous
I was wondering if it would be a good idea to take on another case...
uh
senior
Is this what you came here for?
Why do you make me hide behind my senior?
We broke up
I don't want to do that
and
Then it's better
What?
Because I can be the bait
[Prosecutors] Hello
[Seokhyun] Manager, the civil servant you mentioned
I brought it from the police headquarters.
How to handle it?
[Wing - Cell Phone]
[Chief Prosecutor] Yes, Mayor.
[Meaningful music]
yes, i understand
Investigator, let this guy go.
[sigh]
[Investigator clears his throat]
[Investigator] Well, you can go.
[tick tock]
[Click - Moon]
[Bang-door]
[Mansik] Oh, look at this guy.
National Police Agency, Prosecutor's Office
It's like going in and out of my own home.
[Jonghyun] At the prosecution
I admit to the crime of aiding and abetting smuggling, but
It's a minor matter
Only a suspended indictment was issued.
At Inseong Headquarters Customs
Only personnel change and 3 month salary reduction disciplinary action.
That's all I got
Ah, you bastard
What are you really doing, you idiot?
During the investigation
From Minjoong Lee’s data:
Family, hometown, school
Even a little bit with work
People involved, no.
Even the panties he was wearing
Shake it off
There's definitely someone looking after him.
[Coli's 'Your Name']
[Mansik] Inseong Headquarters Customs Surveillance Department
Level 7 Supervisor
I graduated from Korea University
[Jonghyun] Yes
I entered school with a scholarship.
I only attend one semester
I dropped out right away
- [Mansik] Why?
- [Jonghyun] Right after taking a leave of absence
If you look at the application to become a customs official,
I think it's probably because of tuition.
Currently in contact
There are no classmates
I have a good reputation at work too.
strangely
I don't have anyone close to me
At least in the same department
With Yuna Kim
It's all about friendship.
[Jaehong] From Inseong
My family died in an accident when I was young.
I was raised by my uncle.
[Mansik] Same goes for friendships.
They say I don’t have any relatives.
What about wealth?
[Jaehong] 120 million won rented house
Deposit of 56 million won
And there is only one compact car.
[Hannah] Min Joo-young goes to the Korea Customs Service
This is a company I have managed since the day I joined the company.
Among the vehicles that Monkey and his gang imported and exported
They said they couldn't find some of them.
When compared to the ledger
About 30 cars are empty.
They are all high-end foreign vehicles.
[Roaring]
[squeak]
[The family’s friendly words]
- [Child] ♪ Dad, cheer up ♪
- [Child’s mock laughter]
♪ There we are ♪
[Ai Mo] I’m good at it.
- [Child] ♪ Dad, cheer up ♪
- [Car acceleration sound]
[squeak]
[Family screams]
There's a swarm of flies.
To Russian guests
Some business partners
Tell them to sort it out.
[Crackling]
Um, my ears are ringing
I feel a little dizzy
I don't think the speed is good
Ah
Are there any medications you usually take?
Uh, did you take painkillers or something sometimes?
Now, what kind of painkiller?
I don't know
Uh, when I looked it up, what did it say?
Ah
They say it's Meniere's syndrome.
Who are you talking about?
Ah...
working in the same department
Our cute bun
[Doctor] Constable, check your condition.
Talk to me
Oh, I'm fine.
- It doesn’t hurt?
- [Dongju] Yes
It must be quite painful
Hey, with something like this
Sir, I was the champion.
boxing gold medalist
Energizer Yoon Dong-ju!
yes, i understand
Please sign up for a hair examination.
[Humorous sound effects]
Uh, detailed inspection.
Let's try a few more things.
- Looking at it, the nutrition is a bit unbalanced.
- [Dark Music]
First of all, eat well
Only then will the cracked bones
It will heal quickly
Don't just eat eggs
Because there is a lot to check
First, a few more days
Watch the progress...
Now, Mr. Yoon Dong-ju.
[Anchor/Video] Luxury sports car
A car is driving down the road
The speed recorded by the speed camera is
Over 200 km/h
That red sports car...
[Anchor/Video] Ignoring the signal
A frantic sprint took place
Because of sports cars
A vehicle crashes into a street tree
A major accident...
Uh, on the smuggling list.
It's one of the missing cars.
[Nurse] It’s time to get the shot.
Dongju Yoon
A, Mr.
[Tinnitus beeping]
[Dongju] Yes, indeed
Even after ignoring the law like that,
If you see that it's not cut
What a great person.
Okay
recognition
Eat a balanced diet
To do a lot of bad things
But do you eat alone?
You don't have any friends?
originally like you
A guy who looks different on the outside but is different on the inside
I'm instinctively reluctant
It's hard to get close
[Sweet - toilet paper]
How old are you?
One million thirty-two, why?
It's young
Then you can be my friend.
Wow
Just in case you don't know, I'll tell you one thing.
[Tense music]
If a traffic accident occurs
You will be held criminally and civilly liable.
for an amicable resolution
We come to an agreement.
I won't do it, never
I don't know what kind of strength you have
If you don't agree
you are in prison
Like you said, I did that
I have a strong supporter
Do you think that's possible?
Do you know Ali?
muhammad ali
He did it
‘Impossible Is Not Something’
'Impossible, that's nothing'
Meanwhile, at the bottom of humanity
how dirty you are
I don't know if I've done it
Since I came to Inseong
You can never escape from my ring
[Jooyoung] Hmm...
[Dongju] Tsk, haha
Well, now with my injury
I think I'll give you some time
Let’s see each other often in the future
Don't be a picky eater
Ha...
[Doctor] Your nutrition is a bit unbalanced.
First, eat well.
Only then will the cracked bones
It will heal quickly
Don't just eat eggs
- [Sizzling]
- [Dongju] Yes
If you want to catch that bastard, you have to eat well.
Strange these days
You're just taking Yamseng's side, huh?
um
[Mansik] Hey!
[laughter]
Waha, wahaha!
you are in the hospital
I told you to stay still, huh?
What are you doing in the office now?
No, he's cool.
What do you do when you're lying in bed?
Only the hospital bills are broken.
What is that?
Mine?
Don't be funny, okay?
Just from home shopping, eh?
1+1, buy mine...
Thank you, I will eat well.
Sheesh, hahaha
Wow, this...
Look at the smoke
This is a meat restaurant, this is, ok.
[Joyful music]
[Dongju] One, two
- [Mansik] Hmm
- [Dongju’s laughter]
Daebang is delicious
There's no pepper
[Sparkling sound effect]
Oh, I'm crazy.
Hey!
hello
You went to work, are you feeling okay?
As you can see
[Jonghyun] You...
Hello...
- [Jonghyun] Yoon Dong-ju, you are reading my book...
- [Dongju] Ah...
Oh, what was this morning, huh?
- [Small] Put it away.
- [Small] Let’s clean it up together.
[Interesting music]
[Mansik] Go, take it.
Take it, take it, take it
I'm sorry, bro.
Aha
Here, why does it smell like this?
Write it, ha
[Sparkling sound effect]
It smells so good
It's better, right?
[Hannah] Oh my
Kid...
Hehehe
child, Mr.
trying to save someone
Did you hurt your arm like this, huh?
I told you to eat well to build strong bones, but tsk.
[Soft music]
Hehehe
Hmm
Now
eat
[Bong - Boat horn]
[Jonghyun] Jinsu Lee’s documents
Maybe you think you saw it?
Do you remember what it was?
Hey, you eat all of this, eat a lot.
[Crack, tap, tap]
Well, now Dongju is here too.
Let's plan the future, uh.
[Dongju] Has Hannah come in yet?
So, where is Inspector Ji?
[Jonghyun] I went out with you
[Meaningful music]
[Hannah] Then it was better.
Because I can be the bait
Ha...
[Hannah] I’ve been looking for it for a long time.
Sometimes when competing
Sometimes you can't see the target
where is it and how far is it
I can't even guess
It's definitely in front of me
Everything seems blurry
At times like that, take a deep breath
Gaze at one place without distraction
Then it comes to mind
Clear and clear
Where I'm aiming
my target
gift
No, you bastards
Following Hannah around
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm talking to you
Does anything change?
Ah...
It's Hannah
[Hannah] Hey, don’t overdo it.
Have you come to meet Minjooyoung?
[Hannah] Yes
[Jaehong] Awesome
[Jonghyun] What did you do?
Jinsu Lee had
blue round circle seen on document
It was this
[Mansik] Cheong Fu, Haeil
Cheongil Shipping
Established in 1972
After going bankrupt in 2009,
It was absorbed and merged.
Min Joo-young at Inseong Headquarters Customs
It's a company I've been in charge of for a long time.
I guess it has something to do with this guy.
Good job
yes
Ah, we figured it out thanks to Hannah.
Good job, Hannah.
But it's dangerous alone
Come with me next time, okay?
[Mansik] Oh my
[Daeyong] I thought you were depressed
I think you found out something interesting?
[Nervous music]
[tick tock]
[Hannah] Try running away, do your best
Fighting
It's a pretty cute fairy.
[Korean-Chinese]
Well, my brother and the Russian customer are
I said I was going straight to the port.
I received a call
What about Filipino guests?
I picked you up at the airport that day.
Just a cell phone and a car
disappeared
[Tiring - Mobile phone]
[Silver Rabbit’s Laughter]
[Silver Rabbit] Uh, uh, uh, uh!
- [Baekga] Stay still
- [Silver Rabbit] Uh, uh!
[Uji string]
[airplane engine sound]
[Kwasik]
[Breathing sounds]
[Man] Um...
[Russian] My mother’s hometown
I told you to come right from the airport.
The situation here is not so good right now.
Where are you now?
[Mansik] Air conditioning?
- Gwangsu University and us?
- [Daeyong] Yes
[Mansik] The prosecution also has investigation materials
I took it all, but with what?
There's one left
Now
This is called ‘candy’
It's a synthetic drug.
very high purity
It’s a high quality new drug.
Distributed only in parts of Eastern Europe
I think it came to Korea recently.
- [Secret Music]
- This also appeared in Monkey’s stolen goods.
If you follow this drug route
Minjooyoung will get caught too.
I can't just suffer like this.
The police department’s reputation is like this, this, this
It doesn't make sense, this
Ah, but
Why are you helping us?
[Dongju] Write, that’s right, why?
Are you trying to destroy our team again?
Here’s more to peel and eat
No, here
You don't like it? no?
If you don't like it, quit, whatever.
- I'll take it to the drug team.
- [Dongju] Yes?
[Jonghyun] For now,
Let's hear more
What information is there?
[Mansik] Yeah, uh
Sit down, sit down and solve some more
What should I know
Decide whether to do it or not, sit down
Now
[Daeyong clears his throat]
The guy who makes this candy
- [Nervous music]
- Drug Ghost
He is a so-called ‘devil’.
About 190cm tall
Other than being a man
Nationality, age, name
Little is revealed
Among drug addicts
‘He is a spy who escaped from North Korea’
‘Japanese Yakuzada’, ‘Philippine gang’
There are a lot of rumors
They spoke together
There's only one thing to talk about
[Click!]
'When you look at the devil's face'
Knock, ‘die’
[Sharp sound effect]
- [Dreamy music]
- [Breathing sounds]
[Man] What are you?
who got my candy
I told you to make it without permission, right?
Phew!
Do you happen to
Jin, the real devil...
I did it wrong
I just
I just did what I was told.
Really...
Really, that candy?
[Devil] Yes
Do you want to try it?
[Cluck cluck]
[laughter sound effect]
[Devil's hum]
Huh?
Crude, irritating, tsk
[Man's laughter]
Do you like it?
Uh, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
[English] Don’t worry
[Man] Ah...
[English] You will be happy
[The devil sighs]
- [Nervous music]
- Ha...
[Women's screams]
Ha... Ah, Mr.
[Man coughing]
[bright music]
Ah
Ah, Mr.
It's limited
Oh no
[Devil's laughter]
Oh!
[Laughing] Oh!
[Daeyong] Is the rumor true or not?
I don't know, but
No one so far
No one has seen the devil's face
[Nervous music]
[telephone rings]
[Jaejin] Yes, metropolitan investigation team
This is Jaejin Park.
[Devil] This is Kihyeon District 7.
[Devil] Wow
Ah, um...
When will you come?
[Jooyoung]
I told you to come right from the airport.
The situation here is not so good right now.
- Where are you now?
- [Devil] Me?
On the way to catch rats
Some guys
They were selling counterfeit candy
I can't stand fake installations.
Catch those guys first
Um...
Oh, and
To commemorate your return home
Those police officers who give you a headache
I'll clean it all up
[Mansik] Hey, it’s a joint operation.
- Together, together!
- [Daeyong] I know, I know!
- [Wham - Siren]
- Um... what is it?
[Devil's laughter]
Okay, you're just in time.
Well, about this much
[wing]
[Bpiyongbiyang]
[Daeyong] Hey, Gwangsu University is going this way!
[Detectives] Yes
[humming]
Oops
[Urgent music]
- Ah...
- [Man 1] Hey
- Wow, Mr.
- [Devil] Ah!
Hey, hey, I didn't think of this, hey
[Devil] Ah!
[Man 2] Ouch!
[Man 2] Wake up, Mr.
A, Mr.
Ah, sir...
Please save me, please save me
- Please save me!
- [Dark Music]
Oh, oh, oh, it hurts
Ah...
Are you okay?
[Devil] Yes
-Are you hurt anywhere?
- [Devil] Yes
[Jonghyun] Ha...
[sniff]
[Nervous music]
It's oil
Avoid!
Yoon Dong-ju!
- [Dongju] Ah...
- [Devil] Ah!
[Clink]
- Ugh!
- [Dongju] Ah!
[Mansik] Hey, Dongju! Hey, hey!
- [Boom!]
- [Detectives’ screams]
Dongju
[The devil's heavy breathing]
Hold on tight!
- [Mansik] Huh? Hey Dongju!
- [Daeyong] Hey, hey!
[Devil's groan]
[Noisy]
- Hey, just let it go! Let go!
- [Daeyong] Hey, there...
No, no, no
Don't let go, don't let go, don't let go!
eww!
[Beep Beep - Walkie Talkie]
[Mansik’s cough]
Is everyone safe?
What about Dongju?
Dongju arrived safely?
Yes, once I was treated, I went to the office.
[Jaehong] This is why there is no evidence
There won't be any left
[Forensic team leader] The body
Judging from the wound on his neck,
Looks like a scalpel is right.
The other body also has the same weapon.
[Daeyong] From the Philippines
Even the three corpses
There were identical traces
The murder suspect is
It was the devil
Has the devil entered Korea?
- [Daeyong] You don’t know that.
- The devil?
[Daeyong] He could be someone who imitates me
What's in that room?
[Jonghyun’s moans]
They also manufacture drugs here.
[Coughing] The women who were kidnapped
Addicted to drugs
I guess they sold it overseas.
There is only one survivor
[Interesting music]
[clatter]
[Beep]
[Man 1] Leo!
A cub who ate from a dog bowl
Why are you fucking in someone else’s territory!
[Russian] Hello, how are you?
[Man 1] Even on your head
Should I open a hole for you?
[Rattle – shell casing]
[Man 2] Huh? Ugh!
Hey, hey, Leo, save me
I had no choice if I wanted to survive, huh?
You know
Yeah, take all the business here.
From port business rights to distribution
I'll give you everything, okay?
Save me just once, Leo.
Of course
Because it was originally my father’s
[Russian] Traitor
[Russian] The hand that killed my brothers
[Man 2] Ouch!
[Russian] The feet that trampled on the sisters
- [Man 2 moans]
- [Russian] Mouth
[Russian] Mouth
mouth, mouth, mouth
Ah, ah, ah
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
[Man 2 screams]
[Russian] The mouth that deceived my mother
[Bang!]
[clatter]
[Russian] And
The heart that betrayed its father
[clatter]
[Bang!]
[Nervous music]
[Boy's frightened breathing]
[Boy] Don’t come!
I'm going to shoot you, don't come!
Don't come!
How old are you?
seventeen years old
Look
Look look
Listen to what suits you
Don't regret like me
Do you understand?
[Male/Russian]
If you want, can I kill you?
[Daeyong] Men's items around 190 cm
There's more to come
Let’s organize things first and then talk
[Detectives] Yes, I understand.
[Detective] Let’s check first.
[Hannah] Well, what is your name?
[Mansik] My parents
Even if it’s a friend’s phone number
Do you remember anything?
I don't know
I don't remember anything
Oh my
[Hannah] Do you remember what you saw there?
Can you talk about it?
Well, just...
Well, he was a tall man.
About 190?
Those people just fight among themselves
There's a loud noise outside
Suddenly my head...
- Ah, ah, ah, I'm sorry.
- [Jaehong] Hey, it’s okay.
That's because you were very surprised.
[The devil's trembling breathing]
relax a little
Let's ask again
[Mansik] Oh, yeah
[heavy music]
[Devil] Please save me, please save me!
Please save me!
Change into this
The clothes I was wearing are evidence, so here they are
Ah, yes
thank you
- Change your clothes and come out.
- [Devil] Yes
[Man-sik] I’m the only witness who saw the devil.
Safety and security are top priority
First, until the memories come back
Let's take him with us
Request for personal protection
to a safe house
How about moving it?
Internal information will be leaked
Just Gwangsu University and our team.
I think it would be good to know
[Mansik] Ah... that’s right
I can't just leave it here
[Devil]
Oh, you don't have to worry about me.
I'll find a place to stay
If anything happens
I can contact you right away.
[Mansik] No.
Because it's a dangerous situation
We will protect you
Ah, here we are
Sergeant Kim Jong-hyun took charge...
[Interesting music]
Why...
I'll be with you
Rather than being alone
You'll feel safe.
[Hannah] Then rest in peace.
Because I'll be outside
If you need anything, let me know.
ha
Ah...
I'm stuck
[English] Damn, tsk
child
[Wing - Coffee Machine]
[Hannah] Aren’t you going?
[Dongju] How are you going?
A trustworthy police officer
I need to be by your side to calm down
Who is reliable?
Didn't you see it?
Holding on to me like a baby to protect me
I just instinctively recognized it.
Oh, and
Team leader 24 hours a day
I told you to stay together
From now on, the two of us
[Ding - sound effect]
It's a partner
[Soft music]
[Hannah] Since when
I heard you so well
oh
Coffee tastes good too
The atmosphere is good too
Hannah is good too
[Soft music]
[The devil's trembling breathing]
[Dongju] Are you okay?
- [Devil] Ouch!
- [Dongju] Ah!
Hold on tight!
Done
[Beep]
Now, the national representative kimchi stew.
came out
[Devil] Oh!
[Dongju] Big...
Wow, that sounds delicious.
From our Hannah
[Hannah] Yoo Nan-eun
Oh, just eat your lunch box.
[Dongju] Ah, still
I need some hot soup.
Eat it quickly
What do you think?
Isn't it delicious?
Well, it's worth eating.
[Dongju] Even though this seems simple
A boxer's joys and sorrows
Because it's soup
Try eating it with tofu and kimchi.
Meat too
- [Interesting Music]
- [Beep Beep - Microwave]
Yeah
Float, Float, Float...
Write
Oh, come on, come on
Now
Here
Enjoy
- [tuk]
- [clatter]
Ha...
Why?
-Is it strange?
- [Devil] No
It's like a taste I've forgotten for a long time.
Even though my arms are uncomfortable, you even cook for me.
I will eat well
Hey, it's no big deal.
You can easily do this with one hand.
I was in big trouble
You have to eat warm to fill your stomach.
Sleep comfortably and comfortably today
Because I'm protecting you
Nothing will happen
yes, thank you
[The devil's faint smile]
-Thank you
- [Devil] No, enjoy your meal.
But the arms
How did you get hurt?
[Dongju] Oh, this?
Catch the bad guys too
I need to save someone
But I don't know if I'm thankful.
Huh?
Let's eat or something
Oh, I heard you were a boxer.
national team
He said he just won a gold medal.
Well, yes
Wow, awesome
[Dongju] Oh, do you know Ali?
[Devil] Ali?
That ‘Impossible Is Not Something’?
Oh, that's right, 'Impossible is Nothing'
- Oh, right.
- [Devil] Huh! Awesome
How do you know Ali?
[Devil] I know, of course
[Dongju] Haha, wow, it’s amazing
originally everything
I know it's singer Ali.
[The devil, Dongju’s laughter]
Hey
Ah, nice house, huh?
No, having a house like this
Why do you live in an officetel?
No, well, shit.
It's too big to live alone.
It's too far from Cheong.
[Mansik] Ah...
Ah, but
As Sergeant Kim said
I add a dongju, but
It'll be okay, right?
Minjooyoung Lee
They must be aiming for Inspector Ji.
Even witnesses
Now those two are together
It will be safer
We will continue to patrol the surrounding area.
I don't know anything else, but when it comes to protecting people,
Mutts are the best
Hanna's safety
worry
You don't have to.
[light sigh]
Who will protect it?
[Dongju moans]
[Doctor] This car accident
Even if it looks okay now
After a few days, the tension subsides.
You may experience muscle pain or body aches.
To my family
Please tell me to take a good look.
yes
[Doctor] Yes, that’s right.
[bright music]
Hmm...
[sigh]
It's warm
[Dongju] Hmm
A, Mr.
[Hannah]
Chi...
What is it
Oh, isn't this a luxury product? Is it real?
yes, that's right
[Jaehong] Team leader
The head of the police department
They say get ready now.
Ah, that annual event
What's so great?
It's making me unable to work, work, tsk
Let's go
Let's go, let's go
[Click - Moon]
[Rust]
[Shoot - Shower]
Hey, come out quickly, it's late.
[Dongju] Okay, wait a minute.
- [tuk]
- Uh, no, no, no.
- Oh, what should I do?
- [Hannah] Hey, what are you doing?
- hey!
- [Dongju] What should I do with this, Hannah?
[Hannah] Ah, hey
[Dongju] Ah, ah...
- Are you okay? wake up
- [Dongju] I...
- [Hannah] Wake up, ah...
- Oh my, ah...
[Hannah] Lee, Mr.
Thank you
[bright music]
Why is your face red?
who?
- [Dongju] Are you excited?
- Do you want to guess?
- Are you excited?
- do you want to die?
[Dongju] Yes
- Lee, Mr.
- [Dongju] Ah!
Get ready quickly and come out!
[Dongju] No, at least turn on the water, water!
-Hoppang, I can’t see!
- Ugh.
[Devil] Hmm, it looks good.
You two are dating...
No way
Why? You look good together
Trooper Yoon too
I think I like the detective.
Detective too
It didn't seem like I had any feelings.
Me? Him?
Or are you just unaware?
Oh, as long as I don't go crazy
- No.
- I don’t think it’s true.
[Calm music]
If not, I'm glad
Hmm...
That's cool, Officer Yoon.
In today's world
For the girl I like
The man who throws himself away
Where is it so common?
I'm going to visit Cheong for a while.
While we are away
The people at Gwangsu University will take care of you.
[Devil] Ah...
It's okay to be alone
For no reason because of me
I'm causing you trouble.
Think of it as protection and surveillance.
Although I am a witness
was at the scene
Because I'm also a suspect
- [Noisy cicadas cry]
-The weather is nice too.
Celebrating the 42nd anniversary
Our Inseong Police Agency is
- [Click]
- Highly rated by citizens...
Ah, the chair is hotter.
Boy, it's so hot I'm dying
Let's rent a gym
In this scorching sun
What is this doing?
Ah, so
They say the screen looks good.
I'm sitting there talking like a screen shot
Oh, what did the commissioner say?
The prosecution said so
I stirred it up, but it stayed still?
I don't know what it is
The commissioner seems to be in trouble too.
That Minjooyoung
I'm not a regular guy
Hey, the president's son, what is it?
Baby, even if I stab the Jade Emperor in the ass
He's the one who will survive
Fish oil, my ass is ripe
[Panel heat] Without any problems
Celebrating the 42nd anniversary
Citizens day and night
To protect life and property
hard-working police officer
Thanks to you all
To all police officials
Appreciating your hard work
To my family
I would like to express my gratitude
That typeset fever
- There is not much time left in term...
- [Cicadas’ cries are fading away]
[Calm music]
[Dongju] Do you know again?
Because you fell in love with my charm
Will you like me?
[Hannah] What I like about you
No, never
I don't like you
If you're scared, call me
[Devil] Policeman Yoon too
I think I like the detective.
Detective too
It didn't seem like I had any feelings.
Or are you just unaware?
[Cicadas cry]
[Dongju] It’s Hannah
You waited a long time, right?
Hey, what does the Commissioner have to say?
I don't know why you have so many
Right? Didn’t your leg hurt?
Oh, I don't know what you'll like
I brought everything
What do you want to eat? What would you like to drink?
[Hannah/Narration] Am I drunk from the heat?
Am I drunk on something even worse?
Or I
You're crazy
[Young K’s ‘I’ll Become a Tree’]
♪ Stay hesitating ♪
♪ What I couldn't say... ♪
[Dongju/Narration]
Total record: 61 matches, 56 wins, 5 losses.
left behind a great history
legendary boxer
made everyone kneel
Muhammad Ali had nothing to be afraid of
♪ A thousand words
A thousand eyes ♪
♪ The lush night forest... ♪
[Music fading]
[dark music]
That kind of information
One day in June 2016
After suffering from Parkinson's disease
passed away
[Young K’s ‘I’ll Become a Tree’]
♪ You can rest ♪
♪ On top of my shoulders ♪
♪ Looking at you with your head buried in silence ♪
♪ The sound of my heart
I'm afraid I'll wake you up ♪
♪ Love will find a way
I'll become a tree ♪
♪ For you ♪
♪ Every day is the same... ♪
[Jooyoung] I’ll handle it without any problems.
don't worry too much
Counter punch!
[Hannah] I’ve been with my mom all this time
Have you been in contact?
[Daeyong] That woman’s statement was correct.
[Forensic Team Leader] Since the founding of the country
I think it would be the largest in the country?
Well, now it's all revealed
Let's go and arrest him.
I put it all in.
[Jonghyun] It's not that easy
[Man] For things like this
Get caught up in it!
Ah, I remembered
Me?
What should I do?
[Devil] I have a friend
Special team leader's daughter
♪ You can rest ♪
♪ On top of my shoulders ♪
♪ Without a word... ♪
[Heo Seong-jin’s ‘Finish Line’]